I ate seven pints of ice cream this week
and was still in a caloric deficit.
Here's how I did it. I used my Ninja
Creamy to recreate higher protein, lower
calorie versions of my favorite ice
cream flavors. Here are five of the
pints I made this week. I decided to
recreate my favorite Ben & Jerry's
flavors this week. So, we started off
with the Tonight Dough. This was a
chocolate base with Oreos mixed in and
the Tonight Dough cookie dough pieces
mixed in. Then, I made a strawberry
cheesecake flavor. This was a strawberry
base with graham crackers and
freeze-dried strawberries. Then I
recreated the milk and cookies flavor,
which is a vanilla base with Oreos and
chocolate chip cookies mixed in. If you
didn't know, Halfbaked is Ben & Jerry's
most popular flavor. So, that's what I
did next. And then I did my favorite
flavor of all time, fish food, which was
a chocolate base with chocolate,
marshmallows, and caramel. Absolutely
delicious.